Efstratios Avagianos

Web Developer

Hi, I'm Stratis! I'm a 24-year-old junior-mid and i am Front-end and Unity Developer. I've successfully built and implemented various software applications, and I'm adept at working with APIs to complete ambitious projects. My passion, attention to detail, and fresh perspective set me apart. Right now, I'm looking my next job possition as a Front-End Developer.



- xtratosav1999@gmail.com
- Piraeus, Greece
- in linkedin.com/in/stratis-avagianos798753231

- +30 6971951090
- avagianos.ddns.net
- github.com/ava1313

EDUCATION

Computer Science

Athens University of Economics and Buisness

09/2017 - Present

Athens, Attiki, Greece

PERSONAL PROJECTS

ReLeaf Website (04/2023 - Present)

 ReLeaf is an under development philanthropy organization. I have completely designed the website(not yet published) and added a lot of features to make it look stylish and modern.

Travel Blog Website (02/2023 - Present)

Stravel Blog is a travel-focused sited, built with HTML, CSS, and JS.
 It features modern technologies like Bootstrap and a parallax scrolling landing page. Although still in development, it's hosted on my Raspberry Pi via DDNS, using Node.js and a reverse proxy with NGINX.

My Portfolio

 Check my portfolio page avagianos.ddns.net . This page is built with HTML Css and JavaScript. It is hosted on my Raspberry Pi board. It utilizes technologies like docker,nginx and many more. Feel free to contact me for more info.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Assistant Accountant

Black Ice Inc

02/2022 - 10/2022

Igoumenitsa, Thesprotia, Greece

Sales Assistant

Black Ice Inc

02/2022 - 10/2022

Igoumenitsa , Thesprotia , Greece

Waiter

Balloni Beach Bar

06/2021 - 08/2021 Thermi, Lesvos, Greece

Web Developer

Darc

10/2023 - Present

Athens, Greece

Darc.ai is a advertising company. My role there is to create websites using Wordpress.

SKILLS



CERTIFICATES

Michigan Certificate of Proficiency (05/2021 - Present)

Vellum Certified Game Developer with Unity (08/2022 - 10/2022)

LANGUAGES

English

Greek

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

German

Limited Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Fishing Hiking Gaming Soccer Painting

Scuba Diving | Photography

hy | Videography